{
    "id": "d09e00f3a0dd4c50956f8f3c94c1fd50",
    "title": "Tenses | Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It ...................... raining for two hours.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has been",
                "have been",
                "is",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... .. my grandmother yesterday.",
            "description": "We use the simple past tense to talk about something we did in the past. ",
            "answers": [
                "visited",
                "have visited",
                "had visited",
                "was visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My boss ..................... from London.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "returned",
                "has returned",
                "had returned",
                "have returned"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "See that you ..................... . on time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will arrive",
                "would arrive",
                "arrive",
                "arrived"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She will come if you .....................…… her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "invite",
                "invited",
                "would invite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I .....................…… to Iceland recently.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "have been",
                "had been",
                "Either went or had been"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor concluded that the man .....................… killed ten hours ago.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "have been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We ..................... . waiting for them for two weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have been",
                "had been",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The train .....................…. before we reached the station.",
            "description": "We use the past perfect for the earlier of the two past actions.",
            "answers": [
                "will leave",
                "will have left",
                "had left"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I ....................... the newspaper every morning.",
            "description": "We use the simple present tense to talk about habitual actions in the present. ",
            "answers": [
                "am reading",
                "will read",
                "read",
                "have read"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}